Congratulations on making it to the
end of this short course.
In summary,
in this short course you've
learned about two key
principles for prompting. Write
clear and specific instructions, and
when it's appropriate, give the
model time to think. You also
learned about iterative
prompt development and
how having a
process to get to the prompt
that's right for
your application is key. And we went
through a few capabilities of large
language models that
are useful for many applications, specifically
summarizing, inferring,
transforming, and expanding.
And you also
saw how to build a
custom chatbot. That was a
lot that you learned in just
one short course, and I hope
you enjoyed going through
these materials.
We hope you'll come up with some
ideas for applications that
you can build yourself now. Please
go try this out and let us know
what you come up with. No
application is too small, it's fine
to start with something that's kind of
a very small project with
maybe a little bit of
utility or maybe it's not even useful
at all, it's just something fun.
Yeah, and I find playing with
these models actually really fun,
so go play with it!
I agree, it's
a good weekend activity, speaking
from experience.
Uhm, and just, you know,
please use the learnings
from your first project
to build a better
second project and you know,
maybe even a better third project,
so on. That's kind of how I have
kind of grown over time
using these models myself as
well.
Or if you have an
idea for a bigger project already,
just go for it. And you know, as
a reminder, these kind of
large language models are a very
powerful technology, so it kind of
goes without saying that
we ask you to
use them responsibly and
please only build things
that will have a positive impact.
Yeah, I fully agree.
I think in this age,
people that build AI
systems can have a
huge impact on others. So it's
more important than ever
that all of us only use these tools
responsibly. Uhm, and I think building
large language model
based applications is just a very
exciting and growing
field right now. And
now that you've finished
this course, I think
you now have a wealth of knowledge that
let you build things
that few people today
know how to. So, I hope
you also help us to spread the word
and encourage others to
take this course too. In closing,
I hope
you had fun doing this course, and I
want to thank you for
finishing this course. And both
Ezra and I look forward to hearing about
the amazing things that
you build.